Silent Bob Speaks.
An Evening with Kevin Smith is a comedy,
documentary film directed by J.M. Kenny.
Kevin Smith interacts in Q&A sessions throughout
various college stops in the USA.
Himself, played by Kevin Smith.
Himself, played by Jason Mewes.
Himself, played by Scott Mosier.
An Evening with Kevin Smith is a DVD featuring question and answer sessions that the comedian and
filmmaker Kevin Smith held with his fans at various American colleges in 2001/2002.
The colleges were: Clark University, Cornell University, Indiana
University, Kent State University and University of Wyoming.
During the sessions, Smith answers questions
regarding his movies, as well as his life.
He discusses how he got started in the movie industry, how different films came about, his friendship
with Jason Mewes, and his relationship with the media, fans, and various other celebrities.
The tone is lighthearted.